klariti.com 2018-06-29

# Klariti – Privacy Policy

Thank you for using Klariti. This Privacy Policy explains our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information that we receive when you use this website and our iOS application.

This policy is effective from September 2007.

_Last updated: July 10th 2016_

Klariti operates at [http://www.klariti.com](http://www.klariti.com/) (‘Site’). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

This Privacy Policy only applies to Klariti and doesn’t apply to anyone else’s websites, services, or applications, even if you can access those through Klariti.

## Information Collection And Use

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name (“Personal Information”) and email address.

## Information Collected using Cookies

We collect certain information through the use of “cookies,” which are small text files that are saved by your browser when you access Klariti. We may also use cookies to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing and to customize and improve Klariti. Although most browsers automatically accept cookies, you can change your browser options to stop automatically accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting cookies.

## Information Related to the Use of Klariti

Our servers automatically record information about how a person uses Klariti, including IP addresses, browser types, operating systems, pages or features of Klariti that were used and time spent on them, search terms and other statistics.

We analyze this information using Google Analytics to customize and improve Klariti.

## Information We Share With Third Parties

Payments are made using third-party service providers that requires it, such as for payment processing, data storage, and hosting and servers.

  * We do NOT have access to your financial details at any point
  * We do NOT share your data, such as your email address
  * We do NOT collect geo-location data from your mobile device
  * We do NOT collect your mobile device photos or photo gallery

We DO share data with:

Law enforcement or authorized third parties to investigate criminal activity or violations of our user agreement.

**Note** : We reserve the right to disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials if it is necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation or legal process; to respond to lawful requests; to protect the rights, property and safety of us or others; and to prevent or stop illegal activity.

## Newsletter and Communications

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials.

We will NEVER spam you.

Your email address is never shared with other companies. If you sign-up to our newsletter (provided by Aweber) , you can unsubscribe with one click.

## Our Policy Towards Children

Our website is intended for IT and business professionals. It is not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from users in this age group. If we learn that we have collected person data of a child under 13, we will take steps to delete such information from our files as soon as is practicable.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

Any information that we collect is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time such information is collected. We may, however, revise the Privacy Policy from time to time. If a revision—in our sole discretion—is material, we will notify you (for example via email to the email address associated with your account). Other changes may be posted to our blog, so please check that regularly. The most current version will always be posted on our Privacy Policy page.

## Complaints

Klariti commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. Inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Klariti at:

Klariti Ltd

63 Ripley Hills

Killarney Road

Bray

Co Wicklow

Ireland

info@Klariti.com

## Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@klariti.com.
